For everyone who's ever been deeply in love or deeply in debt.
The Money Pit is a comedy, romance film directed by Richard Benjamin.
After being evicted from their Manhattan apartment, a couple buy what looks like the home of
their dreams—only to find themselves saddled with a bank-account-draining nightmare.
Struggling to keep their relationship together as their rambling mansion falls to pieces around them, the two
watch in hilarious horror as everything—including the kitchen sink—disappears into the Money Pit.
Walter Fielding, Jr., played by Tom Hanks.
Anna Crowley, played by Shelley Long.
Max Beissart, played by Alexander Godunov.
Estelle, played by Maureen Stapleton.
Art Shirk, played by Joe Mantegna.
Curly, played by Philip Bosco.
The Money Pit is a 1986 American comedy film directed by Richard Benjamin and starring Tom Hanks and Shelley Long
as Walter Fielding and Anna Crowley, a couple who attempt to renovate a recently purchased house.
The film is a loose remake of the 1948 Cary Grant comedy film Mr.
Blandings Builds His Dream House, and was filmed in New York City and
Lattingtown, New York, and was co-executive produced by Steven Spielberg.
The film explores themes of rock star, chaos, price, house, home ownership.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.